# **Cameron Morales**

## Software Developer

- 708-845-0107
- cam.morales93@gmail.com
- https://github.com/Camm66

An adaptable computer science graduate student with 3+ years of academic programming experience, currently seeking an internship or entry-level position. Eager to leverage a passion for mastering new techniques and technologies throughout the various design and development stages of your software solutions.

## **Education**

2016-09 - present

#### DePaul University, Chicago IL

M.S. Computer Science

GPA 3.63 / 4.0

**Areas of Study**: Object Oriented Development, Software Architecture, Database Technologies, Web Applications, Distributed Systems, Cybersecurity.

#### 2011-09 - 2015-06

#### Columbia College, Chicago IL

B.A. Audio Design & Production

GPA 3.71 / 4.0

Areas of Study: Live Sound Mixing, Studio Recording, Signal Processing, Sound Design/Synthesis

# থ্য

### **Skills**

- Languages: Java, Python, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, SQL/NoSQL
- Frameworks: Flask, Angular
- Software: Eclipse, NetBeans, SQL Developer, Wireshark, MSOffice
- Operating Systems: Linux, Windows 10
- Version Control (Git)
- Excellent Customer Service
- Strong Communication and Collaboration

# Q

### **Certificates**

2017-08

- COMPTIA Security+ Certification
- **2018-08** Uda

# Udacity Full Stack Web Developer Nanodegree

## **Experience**

#### 2017-07 - 2018-08

#### Perishables Buyer

Whole Foods Market

#### Responsibilities:

- Ordered, replenished, and merchandised perishable products and participated in regional and national sales promotions.
- Maintained and monitored department waste, spoilage, and transfer logs.
- Managed Yearly Comps of 20% during peak holiday season.
- Oversaw implementation of the new 'Order-To-Shelf' standard operating procedures.

#### 2015-11 - 2017-07

### • Grocery Team Member

Whole Foods Market